[
    {
        "question": "My car always ............ down on the motorway.",
        "choices": [
            "is broken",
            "has broken",
            "breaks",
            "was broken"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "breaks"
    },
    {
        "question": "I think the next train to Aswan ............ at 10 a.m.",
        "choices": [
            "will leave",
            "leaves",
            "is leaving",
            "left"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "will leave"
    },
    {
        "question": "One of the Egyptian scientists ............ awarded the Nobel Prize in 2010.",
        "choices": [
            "was",
            "has been",
            "were",
            "had been"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "has been"
    },
    {
        "question": "When I was in Sharm El-Sheik, I ............ to the beach a lot.",
        "choices": [
            "have gone",
            "was going",
            "would go",
            "went"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "went"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yesterday, we ............ some beautiful fish in the Red Sea.",
        "choices": [
            "saw",
            "were seeing",
            "see",
            "have seen"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "saw"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nesma ............ late when she was young. She no longer does now.",
        "choices": [
            "usually sleeps",
            "c.used to sleep",
            "b.is used to sleeping",
            "d.was usually slept"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "c.used to sleep"
    },
    {
        "question": "My sister usually ............ to school when she was young.",
        "choices": [
            "walks",
            "was walking",
            "walked",
            "has walked"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "walked"
    },
    {
        "question": "Money ............ into our country by tourists who come to enjoy our civilization.",
        "choices": [
            "is brought",
            "has brought",
            "are brought",
            "is bringing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is brought"
    },
    {
        "question": "Every day, my room ............ while I'm at school.",
        "choices": [
            "was tidied",
            "is tidied",
            "tidied",
            "was being tidied"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is tidied"
    },
    {
        "question": "When he went on holiday, he always ............ a lot of photos .",
        "choices": [
            "takes",
            "have taken",
            "took",
            "has taken"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "took"
    },
    {
        "question": "He committed the crime and ............ away.",
        "choices": [
            "runs",
            "ran",
            "run",
            "running"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "ran"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tamer ............ meals outdoors .",
        "choices": [
            "hasn't",
            "never has",
            "has ever",
            "isn't had"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "hasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "Now, Salah ............ as a role model for all young Egyptians.",
        "choices": [
            "is being known",
            "is known",
            "knows",
            "known"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is known"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much time ............ on social media?",
        "choices": [
            "are spending",
            "you spend",
            "is spent",
            "spent"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is spent"
    },
    {
        "question": "He ............ hard work on the farm.",
        "choices": [
            "used to",
            "were used to",
            "got used to",
            "didn't use to"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "used to"
    },
    {
        "question": "My friend used to get high marks but now he ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "don't",
            "doesn't",
            "didn't",
            "isn't"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "He ............ at the club yesterday.",
        "choices": [
            "isn't seen",
            "wasn't seen",
            "didn't see",
            "doesn't see"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "wasn't seen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do as you ............ and don't ask questions .",
        "choices": [
            "tell",
            "are told",
            "are telling",
            "being told"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "are told"
    },
    {
        "question": "Never ............ to school late. He is so punctual.",
        "choices": [
            "he comes",
            "comes he",
            "does he come",
            "is he come"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "he comes"
    }
]